burningman.com 2014-06-25

# Burning Man :: Privacy Policy

**WHAT THIS POLICY COVERS**  
This policy covers personal information that we receive when you use the burningman.com site.

“Personal information” is information that can be linked to you as an individual, such as your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number. By visiting this web site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**INFORMATION YOU KNOWINGLY GIVE TO US**  
We receive and may store any personal information you actively send us or enter on our web site. You provide such information when you register for a Burner Profile; register for the ePlaya community boards; register as an Image Gallery or Playa Artifacts contributor; fill out an online registration or other form; submit images, contribute to Tales from the Playa, or ePlaya discussions; sign up for our mailing lists or newsletter distribution lists; or send us e-mails. You also enter personal information when you purchase tickets to the Burning Man event or other items online at our web site. Other information you enter, such as your survey responses, are only compiled statistically and are not recorded permanently or in a personally identifiable way.

**INFORMATION THAT IS AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED BY OUR SYSTEM**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us through the internet.

We use a cookie to store your login ID and password and to synchronize your responses to one questionnaire with other relevant questionnaires. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to allow our system to recognize your browser and to provide you certain browsing conveniences. You can configure your browser to reject cookies, but if you do so, you might not be able to experience all the interactive features of our web site.

**GOOGLE ANALYTICS**  
We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to maintain and improve the site’s technical performance. Google Analytics collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of service, available at <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html>, and the Google Privacy Policy, available at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.

**WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We use the personal information that we receive to operate the web site, produce the Burning Man event, and for Burning Man-related projects. Your personal information may be stored on our system and shared among Burning Man affiliates, including but not limited to the Burning Man Project, Black Rock City, LLC, and Black Rock Arts Foundation. We do not rent or sell your personal information to any other entity. We do not share your personal information with any other entity, except when: 

  * We have your permission; or
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; or when we must exercise our legal rights, protect our property, defend against legal claims, or otherwise comply with the law; or
  * We believe it is appropriate in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud, threats to personal safety, or violation of this web site's terms of use.
  * When you order tickets to the Burning Man event and other items on line at this web site, your order is processed in collaboration with TicketFly, a separate company. The information you submit in connection with your online ticket order is governed by TicketFly's privacy policy.

Burning Man and/or the Black Rock Arts Foundation may at times contact you at your email address to keep you informed about their local events and other Burning Man related opportunities. Should you not want to receive such communications, you will find details about how to opt out the first time you are contacted.

If Burning Man is acquired or transferred, or changes entity status, the personal information maintained on the Burning Man system will be among the transferred assets but will remain subject to any Burning Man privacy policy in existence at the time of the acquisition or transfer.

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**  
The only people who have access to personal information collected on this web site, either directly, or through use of Google Analytics, are employees who have a need to know and who are bound by nondisclosure agreements and this privacy policy. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the personal information that we store.

However, whenever you submit expressive content to areas of our website such as the Image Gallery, Playa Artifacts, Tales from the Playa, or ePlaya, you understand that the submission will be made public on the web site, and that such submission may contain personal information. We are not responsible for the personal information that you or others choose to post in this manner. You may be identified as the author of any posted expressive content unless you tell us otherwise.

We will identify your ePlaya submissions by the handle you register and will not disseminate any other registration information without your authorization. However, if you contact other posters by e-mail, your personal information may be included in the header, as with any e-mail.

In general, we cannot guarantee your anonymity whenever you interact with our web site.

Please note that the burningman.com web site may contain links to third party web sites. These third party web sites may send their own cookies to collect data and solicit personal information. Therefore, we cannot guarantee your privacy when visiting such third party sites, nor the accuracy or acceptability of any services provided by such third parties.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
We may update this policy from time to time. When any significant changes are made to this policy, we will post a notification in a prominent place on this web site so that you may be made aware of the changes. This notification will appear the first time you log on to this web site following a significant change in this policy.

**HOW YOU CAN MAKE CHANGES TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ON OUR SYSTEM**  
You can edit personal information in your Burner Profile by logging on to our system and manually editing your Burner Profile page, or by sending a description of your requested change through the “Contact” link on our web site.

**EFFECTIVE DATE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
This policy is effective as of February 14, 2013.
